[
    {
        "front": "あかるい",
        "back": "明るい \nbright",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつめい",
        "back": "説明 \nexplanation",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "あした",
        "back": "明日 \ntomorrow",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "はつめい",
        "back": "発明 \ninvention",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "くらい",
        "back": "暗 \ndark",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんこく",
        "back": "暗黒 \ndarkness",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "あんごう",
        "back": "暗号 \nsecret code, cryptography",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "とおい",
        "back": "遠い \nfar",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "えんそく",
        "back": "遠足 \nexcursion, picnic",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちかい",
        "back": "近い \nnear",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きんじょ",
        "back": "近所 \nneighborhood",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいきん",
        "back": "最近 \nrecently, now-a-days",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "つよい",
        "back": "強い \nstrong",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう",
        "back": "勉強 \nstudy",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうふ",
        "back": "強風 \nstrong wind",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "よわい",
        "back": "弱い \nweak",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゃくてん",
        "back": "弱点 \nweak point",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうじゃく",
        "back": "強弱 \nstrong & weak",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもい",
        "back": "重 \nheavy",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいじゅう",
        "back": "体重 \nbody weight",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうだい (な-adj.)",
        "back": "重大 \nimportant",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "かるい",
        "back": "軽い \nlightweight",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいしょく",
        "back": "軽食 \nlight snack",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふとい",
        "back": "太い \nfat (body)",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいよう",
        "back": "太陽 \nsun",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほそい",
        "back": "細い \nthin, slender",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "こまかい",
        "back": "細かい \nfine, minute",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうさい",
        "back": "詳細 \ndetails",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "さいく",
        "back": "細工 \ncraftmanship",
        "chapter": "N4 K2"
    }
]